The Amanda Seals Show.
Former President Trump vows to demolish the deep state
and reshape the federal government to align with his agenda,
including plans to remove civil service protections,
making executive branch employees fireable at will,
and relocating positions out of Washington.
Let me just say that in layman's terms.
He's basically saying when he comes in office,
he's not going to make it where civil service employees
can keep their jobs and have actual, you know, like rights.
No, he's going to be like, if I don't like you,
I can fire you and it doesn't matter what you say.
Experts warn that Trump's proposals could politicize
the federal workforce, drive out experienced employees,
and lead to corruption, obviously,
because they've also said that he will not hire you back
unless you pay allegiance to him.
What?
Yeah, you got to pledge allegiance to him.
Trump's initiative includes reissuing executive orders
to reclassify civil service workers as political appointees,
potentially affecting thousands of federal jobs.
So, you know, we have people that are in these positions
whether or not it's Democratic or Republican in the presidency,
and he's basically saying,
no, he will get to appoint every person.
So just imagine that everybody working in government
is a supporter of the person in government.
So now that means that there's no objectivity,
there's no checks and balances.
This is a dictatorship.
This is not for play play.
This is Project 2025.
If you haven't Googled, you haven't looked it up,
please do so that you can get more information
about what their plans are.
The Heritage Group is behind this.
We are, we are, we are.